# FLÁVIO LUCAS

# **COMPUTER ENGINEER**

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 

As a Computer Engineering student with over 3 years of experience in web development, I possess skills in both front-end and back-end development, and my portfolio showcases some successful projects. I excel at team collaboration, utilizing agile methodologies and gitflow for code versioning, and I stay up-to-date on the latest industry standards. I'm searching for new experiences in computer engineering and trying to learn more and more day by day.

As an intern, I am eager to contribute my skills to challenging projects and learn from a highly qualified team. I am passionate about web development and always strive to stay on top of emerging trends and technologies. Working alongside a highly qualified team would provide me with valuable learning opportunities and experience that I can carry with me throughout my career. I am confident that I can bring value to the team and look forward to discussing how I can contribute to the success of the company.



# **CONTACTS**

- +55 015 99641-9578
- flavioluca389@gmail.com
- Auriflama, Sorocaba SP

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## 2020 - 2020 L.I.G.A. (as intern)

- Handling and learning different technologies during my day work.
- Developing sites (front-end) and sometimes API's

# 2021- Present L.I.G.A. (as Jr. developer)

- Handling with differents tecnologies as when I was an intern, but with more responsabilities like take care of one voluntary student.
- Dealing with co-workers and praticing team work and relations in work environment.

## LANGUAGES

Portuguese - mother tongue

English - intermediary (B2)

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - Present Facens

Bachelor Degree Computer Engeneering

#### 2018 - Present Internet

• When I realized that I needed experience to really learn how to develop things I started to search and learn by my self in online courses, video tutorials and bootcamps.

#### SKILLS

Angular - Advanced, React - Intermediary, HTML - Advanced, CSS - Advanced, Javascript - Advanced, Python - Intermediary, Typescript - Advanced, CapacitorJS - Advanced, Ionic - Advanced, Electron - Intermediary, HTTP - Advanced, NodeJs - Advanced, TypeORM - Intermediary, NestJs - Intermediary, Docker - Intermediary, C - Basic; C#/Java - Basic, Rust - Basic, SQL (PostgreSQL, mySQL) - Intermediary, noSQL (MongoDB) - Basic.